570-502-0025

brad.a.fox.work@gmail.com

Experienced, highly organized and creative Graphic Designer in marketing, advertising, print design and multimedia. Strong collaborative and interpersonal skills; with well developed written and verbal communication abilities. Highly skilled in client and vendor relations and negotiations; accomplished at building and maintaining "win-win" partnerships. Skilled creator and accustomed to performing in fast-paced, deadline-driven and complex project environments with an emphasis on working within budget requirements.

Creative experience in the following:

Print - Brochures, Logos, Business Cards, Marketing Communications, Trade Show, Advertising **WEB & Multimedia** - Website Design, CSS, HTML, JavaScript, React, Wordpress, Video Editing **Photography** - Landscape/Product/Portrait Photography, Retouching, Photograph Restoration

Professional Experience

Graphic Designer/Production Manager

SpeedPro Imaging Lock Haven, Lock Haven, PA

June 2016-January 2020

- Managed projects and deadlines to meet customer's expectations and visions
- Managed the design and production of client artwork, advertising/marketing materials and installations
- Communicated one-on-one with customers on a daily basis to ensure satisfaction
- Oversaw projects from start to finish to ensure customer's marketing goals
- Multi-tasked many complex projects at once with proper time management to ensure customer satisfaction
- Maintained large format printing and finishing equipment/machines
- Installed signs, vehicle wraps, trade show displays for clients
- Contacted and coordinated all parties needed for codes and proper paperwork
- High accountability in a fast-paced, time sensitive environment
- Ensured that all products designed and produced matched clients' marketing objectives
- Portfolio can be seen on https://bradafoxwork.wixsite.com/bradafox

Graphic Designer

Reese's Print Shop, Lock Haven, PA

January 2005-June 2016

- Created design and layout for shop advertisements, promotions and marketing
- Created customer advertisements, promotions, business forms, marketing materials
- Customer communication on a daily basis to keep customer satisfaction
- Oversaw projects from start to finish to ensure proper output
- Created and designed marketing communications through direct mail campaigns
- Maintained maintenance of printing equipment/machines to ensure proper performance
- Multi-tasked projects with effective time management to ensure customer satisfaction
- Learned to run and maintain various equipment in extremely fast time frame

Art Department Head / Graphic & Web Designer / Computer Technician

JanWay Company, Cogan Station, PA

April 1998-December 2004

- Developed departmental procedures/workflow to ensure quality and maintain archival art files
- Managed progress, deadlines and man-power to accomplish multiple complex jobs
- Designed departmental system for educating/training of standard procedures and workflow
- Created designs/themes for marketing/promotional materials for customers' state-wide programs
- Coordinated with customers and vendors for quality imprinting on promotional products
- Performed IT maintenance/up-keep on network/server (Novell) and terminal computers
- Designed/Oversaw design of web pages for JanWay Company using html
- Website optimization using Search Engine Optimization (SEO)
- Photographed products, enhanced for use in catalogs, flyers, web, and marketing materials

Advertising Internship

Penn College of Technology, Williamsport, PA

September 1997-December 1997

- Designed print materials to promote and market the Student Activities Club's events
- Conducted surveys and analytics of what best caught the attention of the consumer

Freelanced and/or volunteered

- Designed yearly marketing mailer and playbill for Millbrook Playhouse
- Designed/produced Pamphlets, Brochures, Business Cards, Videos, Stickers
- Scholarship, Highlight, Memorable, Photomontage and Sports video production
- Photography Portraits, Landscape, Product
- Fleece-to-Shawl advisor for Sugar Valley Rural Charter School to state competition

Computer Skills

Adobe Creative Suite (Illustrator, Photoshop, InDesign, Dreamweaver, Lightroom, Animate, Premiere Pro, After Effects), Microsoft Office (Word, Excel, Publisher, Power Point, Access, Frontpage), G Suite, QuarkXpress, CorelDraw, Pre-Press Layout/Design, WordPress, Blender, Lightworks, WIX, Cascading Style Sheets (CSS), HTML, JavaScript, Bootstrap, Search Engine Optimization (SEO), Networking, Hardware/Software Installation/Troubleshooting

Certifications

Accenture Digital Skills: User Experience (February 2020)

Google The Fundamentals of Digital Marketing (March 2020)

Google Google for Education Level 1 (G Suite) (July 2020)

freeCodeCamp JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures Developer Certification (August 2020)

freeCodeCamp Responsive Web Design (May 2020)

HubSpot Content Marketing (March 2020)

HubSpot Email Marketing (March 2020)

HubSpot Social Media Marketing (March 2020)

Other Skills

Vinyl / Wrap Installation, Sign Fabrication, Carpentry, Electrical, Plumbing, Fine Woodworking, Printer/Copier Repair, Large Format Printer Operation/Maintenance, Contour Cutter

Education

Pennsylvania College of Technology - Associate's Degree in Advertising Arts